<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dysonsphere</string>

    <string-array name="ArticleTitles">
        <item>Series: 2050: Degrees of Change\nEpisode: Episode 5 - Fire and Forests</item>
        <item>Series: Alberta@Noon from CBC Radio (Highlights)\nEpisode: Monday, November 6, 2018</item>
        <item>Series: All in a Day\nEpisode: Best of All in a Day, Dec 19, 2018: "Blackberry Accelerator Program"</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="podcast_1">This is a CBC podcast. Good morning, Ariadne e. It\'s time to wake up. It is seven A. M. On October fifteenth, twenty fifty. The high end Vancouver will be fifteen degrees. There is an air quality warning in place due to prescribed burn. Garibaldi masks are recommended. Do you know when this burn is supposed to end? Mom was going to take us hiking this weekend. The prescribed burn is expected to last two days. Smoke warning is expected to be lifted by noon tomorrow. Thiss is twenty fifty degrees of change. A CBC Vancouver podcast exploring how climate change will shape our province by the middle of the century. I\'m CBC meteorologist Johanna Waxed. We know firsthand how devastating a wildfire Khun B but by twenty fifty will be facing more fires and more disasters like the wildfire that ripped through Fort McMurray, Alberta, destroying homes and displacing nearly ninety thousand people. From where I\'m standing there ten meters high in the air, just right along the highway. The heat is just absolutely indescribable right now. They would just say it was the biggest smoke I\'ve ever seen. It was just black, like gods. It didn\'t leave and let us take our things when we asked, so we lost everything. Well, that\'s what we have on our backs. I was part of the CDC team who covered the Fort McMurray fire and after a week of intense fire weather forecasting, shifting winds, bone dry conditions and flames so intense they were creating their own lightning. I was sent to the scene no standing on a burn track just outside of Fort McMurray, with smoke still rising in the distance. But it was meeting the people at the evacuation centers, the airport, the gas stations that I will never forget, people who had lost everything. People who worked tirelessly to help in any way they could. People who knew their community would be changed forever. And people who recognized me and ran over to ask if I could tell from the satellite images if they\'re home had been lost to the fire. And I could. Climate change means BC will be facing a longer, more explosive fire season, and that will have profound effects on our forests, our economy and our livelihood. We are in lower Trepagnier Creek, just outside of Peach Land in the Okanagan southern interior BC in what is what. He was historically kind of dry ponderosa pine grassland forest. And today it\'s more of a Ponderosa pine Douglas fir Forrest, So it\'s changed over time. This is Bob Gray. He\'s a fire ecologist who studies the behavior of wildfires. And he\'s brought us here to a clearing near a school in Peach Land to show us what a fire prone ecosystem looks like as we look to the future, well, the research is suggesting that we\'re going to see significantly longer fire seasons. And that means that Mohr fuels were dry out, become available to burn. We\'ll have hotter fires because they\'ll have longer residents. Times crews will have a more difficult time catching fires. Right now. Success rates about ninety seven percent. If we have a longer fire season, we can expect that the success rate will diminish and so more fires will get away. We\'ll have larger fires, so all in all we can see longer fire seasons. Lots more fire in the landscape and the consequences of that with some of the modeling you\'ve been looking at and the way they things have already begun to increases. Faras more extreme Wildfire Days, NBC. Do we have any sense? Like a range of what percentage of extreme fire days were talking about in twenty fifty, some of the models air, suggesting that on the coast we may see coast and temperate force, we may see an increase of one to two days per year kind of extreme conditions. Now that\'s kind of an average annual situation. We will likely see years like twenty fourteen more frequently where twenty fourteen was was a bad year, coastal fire wise and that stretched out over ten or twenty years becomes an average of one additional day, that kind of personality of it. In the interior, we can expect to see that fire season increased by months. I think over the last two decades, some of the research is suggesting the fire season has extended by thirty to fifty days, so we would expect to see that increase a bit more. The North is still a little bit shady about the effects of the model some are suggesting could get wetter. It could get warmer. The pattern we\'re seeing right now the North is that longer fire seasons for sure. The snow\'s coming off quicker. It\'s drawing out quicker and the fire\'s air starting sooner. So and I guess that sort of applies to an increase in triggers a cz well, possibly mohr thunderstorms and maybe more human started fires? Well, certainly if you have a longer fire season, it\'s only a matter of probabilities if you have x number of open ignitions on the landscape cigarettes, car exhaust, catalytic converters, everything else on DH fuels are available. It\'s just a matter of simple probabilities. You\'re going to have more ignitions. Some of the research is suggesting we\'re likely to see more lightning. Another thing that\'s come out of recent research is atmospheric pressure anomalies. Changing, too. So Maura, these blocking high, so sort of stagnating conditions, drying things out but then also like stronger highs. Deeper lows in this Grady Int, resulting in when a system moves on is extremely strong winds. So it\'s really a bad situation that we\'re looking at. Are you worried that will see period? But also before we get there, that will Seymour situations like for Memory and cologne? A few years ago, I think we definitely will. I mean, as things dry out, our ability to catch ceasefires eyes like I says, getting more difficult. We\'re going to see big, big hot fires, very expensive fires in the future. I mean, with all the dead pine we have NBC. We\'ve had some success and harvesting it, but it\'s a big, broad plateau, and it wouldn\'t be out the question to see Million Hector Fire, NBC. It\'s it\'s highly possible. I mean, that was a five hundred thousand Hector fired in Alberta. But it\'s the million Hector fires, just not out of the question. So so that\'s where we start to get worried. That\'s where we start to get worried. You know, throughout the interior, where we have a lot of values on landscape, a ten thousand Hector fire\'s a bad fire. So a million Hector fires was no people. Yes, that weaken. We can deal with that. But even a ten thousand, fifteen thousand Hector fire a lot of values is a bad fire. When fires get hot enough, they actually start to create their own weather, making a dangerous situation even more unpredictable. As intense heat from the ground rises up carrying ash and smoke, they suck up what little water vapor is available and begin to develop like summertime cumulus clouds. The updrafts and downdrafts gets stronger until the tops of these pyro cumulus clouds are towering above thirty thousand feet. In rare cases, thes fire clouds can actually rain on themselves. More often, they create strong shifting winds and lightning that spark new fires and even fire natos. It is every bit as terrifying as it sounds, and large hot fires are already happening more often. So what do we dio? Bob Gray says. The answers, maybe, ironically, more fire by setting controlled burns fire ecologist can help areas from becoming tinderboxes that could turn a fire from a lightning strike into an inferno. We\'re at a point right now where we have a lot of carbon stored on the landscape, and that\'s the problem. And I mean standing here in the sight of interior. We\'re looking at a forest that historically probably had about thirty to fifty stems protector, and right now there\'s there\'s probably close to four thousand. So and historically it was just grass. It was grass and shrubs and herbs. And so if we want this to survive the next fire, the fire needs to be on the ground. So we have to remove all of this excess biomass. And we have to maintain this in that, you know, low density, tree density grass state through repeated, prescribed burning. And we need to do that over large areas. We get to high elevation, and that\'s where we need to basically break up the landscape. So that we have smaller fires in the future and not huge. You know, twenty, thirty, forty thousand Hector fires. So if we re plant species that are more fire tolerant than they\'re able to survive the next fire, if we go back and re plant species like lodgepole pine, they\'re not very fired taller and they\'ll be killed with next fire. And then they become a future fuel here in the Ponderosa pine for us, we need to get rid of Douglas fir and managed for ponderosa pine. In these Cooney\'s, it\'s managing for western large and ponderosa pine, the most to most fire toward species in the province. On the coast, where we\'re going to see some increased drawing and the odd years like twenty fourteen, it\'s it\'s managing for Douglas fir, and it\'s probably being more efficient at suppressing future fires and not letting those fires go. So it really comes down to managing for individual areas. It really is managing it because everything they\'re all complex, each place is gonna have to have its own specific sort of ecological direct standing in this spot right here. It\'s a It\'s a matter of removing all this bio Mass and it has no value. So it\'s a cost. It\'s a huge cost, and it\'s a cost to society to do it. But it\'s also what costs society to not do it. You know, smoke is a huge issue. We talk about doing a lot more prescribed burning and people don\'t want smoke. Thie issue, though, is How do you want your smoke? There is no no smoke option. If we were permitted to doom or prescribed burning, we can just, you know, puke a little bit of smoke in the spring and fall, and you know people can shut their windows and doors and maybe take off for the weekend or something. And we\'re good. We have to do a lot of that. But people are going to have to get used to smoke. And there just is no no smoke option. Of course, this poses a serious public health issue. There\'s a reason people don\'t like smoke. But in the year twenty fifty wildfire smoke is a constant hazard from the early spring through to the early fall. Now here\'s the thing. While fire is terrible for humans, both her health as well for our lively hoods fires aren\'t necessarily a bad thing for forests. In fact, fire plays an important role in forest ecology. Many tree species have adapted to emerge on Lee after a fire sweeps through an area, but climate change may even be changing. That fire is a is a natural process in most of our vegetated ecosystems. NBC. But standing here on the set of interior, I mean, this is really fire adapted ecosystem was historically, fire would come through on a regular basis, sometimes as frequently as every five to seven years. And so many species through evolution adapted to that fire regime. The funny thing standing here is if we had a fire, we came back the next spring, we would find a lot of species that we don\'t currently C here and they have seeds stored in the soil, and it takes heat to scare if I the seed and cause it to Germany. Species like seen office, which is a very important brows, species for deer and elk and somehow those wildlife species. No to go to burn areas because its succulent village plants after fire, and after that top kill, they put all their energy into growth. And no energy into protective enzymes and chemicals, so their foliage is highly palatable for wildlife. Species know that. So everything tends to be kind of focused in on fire. It\'s just amazing how it works. This pyro diversity. It causes diversity. Without it, we lose diversity. How has climate change shifted? That ecosystem has being in place for that natural cycle for centuries. Well, climate change has the has the potential to, um, really negatively affect that diversity. So we\'ve already done damage by taking fire to the system. What he\'s saying is we prioritize putting out fires right away instead of sometimes just letting them burn naturally. Which means when fires do become out of control, there\'s a larger risk that will become more dangerous because of all that dry, dead fuel on the forest floor will keep it burning explosively. The next fire that comes through will likely produce more heat. The threshold of heat in the flux of heating the soil than those species you know adapted to overtime. So through that evolution, they were adapted to a certain level of heat, heat impact, and we\'re going to deliver heat that they\'re just not an aptitude so it\'ll be climate change resulting in a fire and then the fire, resulting in loss of diversity because it\'s a different kind of fire. So in places where we have a less frequent fire regime, we have a fire and the system has time to re balance itself. Resilience that it has a chance to sort of grow back and get comfortable with its surroundings and with climate change. We\'re going to truncate that and bring fire back too soon for the system to kind of adapt to it, and so we\'re gonna have a lot of losers in that one. Here\'s the thing. While people wildlife we can move, trees can\'t. They might live for centuries. And while that means trees have evolved to be hardy and adaptable, the rate of change is happening so fast that trees aren\'t able to adapt with it. Normally, when we think of fire season, you think of the hottest, driest days of the summer and fall. But by twenty fifty, the wildfire season starts early some years as early as April, some fires may smolder all year round. The snowpack simply isn\'t there to keep the forest ground moist enough to keep fires at bay. You remember Darwin Coxon from the ancient forest, that rain forest fuelled by snow rather than rain? Well, he says they haven\'t been able to find any evidence of fire in this thousand year old cedar stand. All thanks to snow. The landscapes around Prince George are dominated by force that typically burned every ninety one hundred years. I moved into a new law in the subdivisions, and when I dug a little pit in my garden. Being a biologist, I could see the little layers of charcoal. But when we come out to these small patches of ancient cedars east of Prince George, when you dig a pit in the soil, there\'s no charcoal layers or the charcoal heirs. When we date, thumb are like every two thousand years, you can find evidence of fires here you\'ll find Ah, big old cedar that has been hit by lightning and has burned up perhaps a tree or two around. It has been charged slowly, but then they fill a load, and what\'s happening is the springs in the CPJ areas. The melt of that snowpack creates a very moist, inhuman conditions in these ancient cedar stands, and it protects them against fires. When you come to the edge of this, these topographic positions you\'re suddenly back into force that air three or four hundred years old. So these air very special places in the landscape that are protected from fire by this linkage to the snowmelt. What do you think will happen Tio this forest by mid century? Were in a new area that has been newly placed into BC provincial park. It were standing in the ancient force. Chanda wanted a provincial park just designated in the summer of twenty sixteen. So if anywhere NBC, this force could survive into the future. It will be here. But a lot depends on what happens to these winter snow packs. We\'ll have some years, no doubt, have normal winters, but we\'re seeing more dry years more melt in the early spring. The records for the the coldest periods we had recently, in fact, are much warmer than cold periods. We had a decade or two ago, so it\'s a landscape that\'s changing in slow motion around us. You are not even that slow emotion. Snow\'s rule is important to forest ecosystems across the province. And even if there are years where we see a return to the high, dense snow packs that provide the moisture trees need climate change brings other threats to our forests. Like pests. Prince George is a community that knows firsthand the devastation pests can cause on forests. The mountain pine beetle affected eighteen million Hector\'s in BC, an area the size of Washington state it had a huge economic cost, destroying nearly sixty percent of pine trees that would have been logged. And forestry is still a major industry. NBC in twenty thirteen it had an economic output of more than thirty one billion dollars. And what we plant right now is what will be harvested in ninety to one hundred years. So it matters that we take a future climate into account. Che Elkin is the mix Would Ecology chair at the University of Northern British Columbia, which we should say is sponsored by the forestry company Slow can because his work has major implications for industry. We met him in a forested area near campus. When we look around us here, we see some beautiful spruce from Aspen, a little bit of older coming in, so really is a mixed would type of force. That is fairly indicative about the force that we see in Central, northern BC Here cheese work looks at climate models and then tries to figure out what that means for future forests and what forest management practices can do to adapt to those changes. </string>

    <string name="podcast_2">This is a CBC podcast. Hi, I\'m Jamie. Puts on For the last decade, I\'ve been a newspaper reporter, and lately I\'m just finding it hard to keep up with the news. As of today, simple possession of marijuana is no longer illegal. It can be hard to make sense of things. Investigators spent nine hours in the consulate\'s appearance or murder. I want to change that. At least a little. I hope you\'ll join me for front burner at daily podcast from CBC News. Subscribe now wherever you get your podcasts. The craziest place for an ad. This is Albert. At noon. I\'m Judy Elvis. Thirty years in the ad world in Terry O\'Reilly has seen some pretty strange sights in Japan, For example, you can place ads on people\'s armpits to students, wiped out their student debt by renting their faces to advertisers. And an S and M store placed ads on the bottom of ketchup bottles. So when you spend the bottles oh, I think you get it. You can hear more stories in just a minute, because Terry O\'Reilly is our guest for the whole hour. So call in to tell us what you\'ve seen. The most unusual location for a ad. Just about seven minutes after twelve. Welcome to the show. He had a great weekends. Maybe even I got caught up on some sleep. Daylight saving Well, Terry, of course, is the host of Under the Influence. It airs weekly on CBC radio. This show is an exploration of advertising in the twenty first century, and it has twenty fifth five million podcast downloads and counting. Now one of the first episodes of the upcoming twenty nineteen season is all about wacky ad placements, so that\'s we\'re going to focus on today. So if you have a baby that triggers a story for you and add, you\'ve seen an unusual location while I want you to give us a call now and you can share it with Terry. One, eight, six, six, four, six, eight, four, four, two, two I\'ll give that phone number again. That\'s number You call if you want to be on the radio with us. One, eight, six, six, four, six, eight, four, four to to send your tweets and tweets are great place because you can also maybe send us a little a little example of what you\'re talking about. That with the picture. Ah, they go two at Albert at noon and emails to Alberta at noon at cbc dot And once again, Terry O\'Reilly in a Toronto studio with us for the hour. Hello. Hello, Judy. How are you? Are really, really great. I\'m so happy we\'re able to join us. Well, thanks for having me. I got a ton of fans I would hear are getting emails from people saying, Terry O\'Reilly. No way. Lovely. So tell us about more about the examples that you we tease the audience with off the top of the show. Well, you know, the Japan example that she heard me talk about briefly. That was really the thing that got me started on chasing down this particular episode. Because so what\'s happening in Japan is, as you may know, in subways there, very crowded. They even hire people to push you and into a subway. So everybody gets on. That\'s how crowded the subways are. So a lot of people have to hold those those railings in the subway exposing their armpits. So some entrepreneurial company saw an opportunity, Judy and started renting out people\'s armpits to put advertising. Oh, my. And I thought that was so crazy an idea that I thought, I wonder what else is out there. And that\'s why I decided, as I said, to explore that in an upcoming episode, I wonder what goes into the right armpit? Well, it\'s funny you say that because I also read that that company is holding auditions to find wonderful armpits, so they have some criteria. Oh, that\'s funny. All right, now, what about the buying of the face? A slate for advertising? Yeah, apparently, there\'s two students in the US They had amassed about eighty thousand dollars in student school debt, so they decided to start a company where they rented their faces. And it was by my face dot com, where they would put logo\'s or whatever on their faces and then go into certain events and, of course, attract a lot of publicity and attention. And it was in one or two years they had wiped out that entire debt. I\'ve also seen the pictures online of sort of other. Like, I guess, body parts for rent hanging from someone\'s beard, beard advertising. Always gotta name Beard thing. Okay, so with the way this one works is you, they actually have little tiny clips and clip a little hanging ad from your beard. And then you walk around the whole day with this thing swimming off your beard as you are. You are. You hope that people wanted to stop and see what? That food in your beard. Oh, no, wait. It\'s an AB that\'s exactly right. Because it\'s so unusual. It gets a lot of attention. And what does all all advertisers want most of all is attention. All right. Okay, Listeners, you recognize the voice? This is your chance to call in and talk with Terry O\'Reilly\'s our guest for the hour. He, of course, host of the very popular podcast and CBC radio show under the influence. And we are talking about the strangest places you have ever seen. A GN ad. And also, you know, I know a lot of these stories might involve locations for ads that actually backfire. So we\'re interested in those stories. Two, one eight six six four six eight for for two two is how you reach us. That\'s a toll free line. Give it again. One eight, six, six four six, eight for four to two. You want to wait? You also teased us about this. This spank the ketchup. Tell us more about that one. So an s and M fetish clothing company wanted to do some marketing. And they have, you know, very limited places where they can place ads. But they came up with this. Very, I think, funny idea where they put stickers for their stores on the bottom of ketchup bottles in restaurants, when people turn the bottles over to, you know, to spank the bottom of the bottle to get the ketchup to run out. They, of course, were spanking. That s and M logo. Which is just such a funny idea to me, it is. But with that work, for like, all the other factors at play, like the ketchup company, would they want that? Well, I think once they\'ve sold, their product is probably the restaurant\'s choice. OK, they want to allow that. And they breast or maybe probably made some money off that. Yeah, Okay. All right. I want to read a quick email that came in. Ah, someone says love under the influence and the age of persuasion. Of course, that was the right. The precursor to under the influence has Terry seen or heard of the herbicide ads on grain bins on the prairies. I have not. Alright, interesting. All right. Well, that came from Rick. Rick, if you if you I want to send us some more details like that, we\'d love to hear if I would. Yeah. Okay. Albert, at noon at CBC Dossier. Make about the phone number One more time, and then we\'ll go to a call. One, eight, six, six, four, six, eight, four, four to two. All right, Julian is on the line now from Edmonton. Julian. Hello. Well, a very good afternoon. A big fan of the podcast, Terry and, of course, Albert at noon. So I was on a holiday with my wife in Europe and, you know, kind of low budget We\'ve wanted to visit Monaco, hopped on a parked car rental car, hopped on a city bus. Then we noticed that the adds up in the bus here in Canada. I\'m used to seeing, like, upgrade your education. You know, those kind of those kind of ads and buses it was for you. Got insurance, Monica. Only in Monaco. That\'s way. Had a good laugh about that one. There were the average person might actually own a yacht. Exactly. Well, you know what? Yeah, that reminds me of I was once approached by a group of nuns to do some advertising for them, which I had never in all my years got a call from from nuns before. But they said, we have this problem that we we\'ve lost our branding. They said, You know, we don\'t wear our habits anymore, so people don\'t think we exist anymore. So women who might have a spiritually calling don\'t know what to do with that. So we need you to get our name out there. So what we did Wass. We created an ad for buses, Justus Julian saying, And it said on it, If you\'re looking for answers, you\'re looking in the right direction. Except we put it on the ceiling or no axe had ever been put before, so and they had the lens logo, etcetera. So there\'s a lot of opportunities in transit. Believe it or not, I\'m Yeah, I wouldn\'t have known that a nun\'s hada brand, but I guess I know I know, very savvy and very smart. We had a meeting and they were very, very you know, educated on what it took to get a brand out like they were. They said, we\'re fans of your show. We listen all the time. We make notes, and there you go. I\'m wondering, Terry, like what would drive? And I\'m thinking on sort of some of the more outrageous idea is that you, You know, the armpits or the hanging from the beard, the beard advertising? It\'s also bald ver ties ing, right? Yes, just close to my heart. Judy, by the way. So same thing where you can put a logo on someone\'s bald head. And again, it\'s just the novelty of it that gets attention. But what look would drive an agency to put an ad in such an unusual location? Well, that\'s a good question. And here\'s the reason there\'s so much advertising clutter in the world out there now. I mean, the rule of thumb is that we all see between thirty five and six thousand commercial messages a day. And if I say to you, Judy, what ads do you remember from yesterday and my struggle with that and that Think about how much wasted money there is. So advertisers are constantly looking for ways to break through the clutter. So one of those ways is to show up on a bald head or in a beard or on someone\'s armpit because it\'s so unusual. It\'s not in traditional media that it gets attention and ah, and you know that it breaks through the clutter. The downside, of course, is that it adds more advertising to the world where every square inch has got an ad or some message on it. That\'s the downside. I thought. You\'re going to say the downside is that your ad might be in somebody\'s armpit on a subway in Japan like, Isn\'t. Isn\'t there a risk about where you might want, even even if it grabs attention, that it might give the wrong message about bringing in? I think I think a brand would have to pick and choose what works with them. Like, for example, if it was some kind of, you know, toilet product, like a bathroom product, that might be a smart place to advertise. You know, if it was toothpaste or shaving cream or whatever. Yeah, or razors. Razors? Okay, All right, all right. The number to call one, eight, six, six four six, eight four, four two to the most unusual ad you have seen. Give us a call. You could talk to Terry, see if he has seen what you\'ve seen. One, eight, six six four, six eight for four, two two. Robert has tweeted in a big fan of Under the influence, he writes. A big rock brewery will stack large, round bales of hay and then wrap them like a beer can. Well, that\'s funny. Yeah, Placement is along. Roadways. I\'ve not seen that have. Have you ever heard of this one? Mandatory? But, well, something that similar that we talk about in this episode is in England. There\'s a lot of train travel, and there\'s a place called train line dot com that promises to save people up to forty percent off their train tickets. So what they did, because you\'re passing lots of meadows and fields on the train. They put ponchos on sheep that said, forty three percent. Also, as you\'re going by all these herds of chef sheep, you\'re saying all these cheap wearing these ponchos? That\'s advertising that claim There they will plot Jos. I don\'t know. I don\'t know. The sheep would appreciate the irony and half what they Well, you know, this whole this whole area we\'re talking about today is called ambient advertising, meaning that in our in my industry, it\'s ambient meeting. It\'s it\'s it\'s in the It\'s out in the In the environment, it\'s not on traditional media, and that would probably qualify his Lamby in advertising. Oh, my goodness. Did you use that one in your podcast? Did I? Of course. I like credit for that later. Good. Good line like that should never go to waste. Okay, here\'s someone has actually tweeted us in Terry. A picture of those big rock bales of hay, fantastic traditional and grass hopper giant bales of hay wrapped like beer cans. That was from Carrie Ann, who tweeted and speaking of ads on the prairie, my co worker from Ontario made me stop during a road trip to take a pic of the beer can Hay bales. That\'s because those hay bales were out there anyway. They\'re probably the right shape. So tell us what would like if you\'re in the ad world like What is that? What\'s the tone that you would want to be striking when you do one of these ambient ads. Well, I think the placement itself is probably pretty bold, and I\'m a big fan of bold advertising. If you listen to my show at all, I\'m always trying to convince advertisers not to do safe, boring advertising. So where it shows up is bold. And then the message itself could be, actually, you know, pretty straight ahead, as long as the where it shows up is outrageous, right? Is, it\'s almost in the in ambient advertising. It\'s where it is almost more than what it iss interesting. All right, Brad in Banff. Hello. Welcome to the show es Brad and bat for you. With us. Yeah. Yeah. You\'re with us here in Albert at noon. Tell us about unusual location for an ad that you\'ve seen. Well, speaking of things carved into the side of things, always remember the green drop carved into the green hill of the side on the trip back and forth the bank. But I was in tracking in the Paul one time about fifteen years ago, before we were carving things on the side of our hair here. And a tracking company had their logo actually basically emblazoned along with the name and the phone number of wealthy tracking number into the side of a yak hair. Yeah, because we\'re in the Mount Everest. Anyway, that\'s that\'s some story. Awesome. Do you? Yeah. Advertising. No. Nice. He just comes. Now we know why you were drawn to this field, Gary. Do you remember? It was just the one yak. And do you remember like, the chatter around it that you would have heard? Well, we first we thought it was some sort of brand, and then I guess it is a brand. But we realized that No, it\'s actually so the logo\'s you\'d see them on. Those particularly act. So looks like only one person was on to that idea. But yeah, you definitely going back and forth up and down the trail. That\'s great. Wow. The actor tiling the actress. Amazing. Yeah. Alright, Brad. Thanks for that. Yeah, thank you. Alright, let\'s goto left bridge now. Adam, in left bridge with us now. Adam. Hello. Hi there. Hey, what\'s the unusual location for an ad that you wanted to tell us about? Well, this this ad is maybe more traditional, but it kind of had a twist to it. So this was about twenty years ago near the airport in Kelowna. And there is a billboard on the side of the road and the top of the billboard looked like it had been damaged, almost as if something had clicked it to run into it. And I was originally more interested in looking at the damage to the billboard. And then I realized that it was advertisement for the Yellow Pages, and the phone book had been turns to flying lessons on the billboard. So funny. So there\'s something that stuck with me for twenty years, and they really had a chance to share in this story. So I thought, This is a great time, All right. And look how you remembered that twenty years later, I mean, that\'s that\'s the what the ultimate goal is An advertising is to create something that has such impact. That you remember it. Not just in the moment, but for a long time past that. So there we are. It\'s been stuck in my head for that long. I love telling that story when I get a chance. All right, Adam. Glad you shared with us today. Thank you very much. You know, Terry were talking a little bit earlier about with that. Sometimes these unusual locations can can backfire to someone has tweeted in a photo. It\'s from Israel, and its sort of the advertisement is for a water company, and the ad reads, Drink eight glasses every day, but it\'s over top under the under the ad, and top of it are bottles of alcohol, right? So instead of storing water in the cooler, they\'re storing booze. So, yes, times when unusual placement for ad doesn\'t necessarily work like how how often do you look at these ads in these sort of unusual locations and think well that that what they didn\'t think through that one carefully? Sometimes I would say more than often more than not, it\'s it\'s actually working. Sometimes you can\'t always decide or you can. You have no control over What you know is beside you when you\'re out there in the in the world putting up anatomy in unusual places, you suggested, like there could be something right beside you that makes your ad ridiculous or or just completely obliterates it. But on the whole, I have to say most of them are either just dull or they really work. Yeah, well, how about how about this one? In the men\'s room, someone has tweeted in in a urinal.</string>

    <string name="podcast_3_bob">This is a CBC podcast. Hi, I\'m Jamie. Puts on For the last decade, I\'ve been a newspaper reporter, and lately I\'m just finding it hard to keep up with the news. As of today, simple possession of marijuana is no longer illegal. It can be hard to make sense of things. Investigators spent nine hours in the consulate\'s appearance or murder. I want to change that. At least a little. I hope you\'ll join me for front burner at daily podcast from CBC News. Subscribe now wherever you get your podcasts. Hi there. I\'m Alan Neil, and welcome to the All in a day podcast where every weekday we try to pick one conversation from today\'s edition of all in a day. So here\'s today\'s now three promising tech companies from Ottawa got some great news Just ahead of the holidays. <b>The Kanada based L Spark teamed up with BlackBerry Q. Nick\'s recently to create an accelerator program with seven spots up for grabs. They choose three local companies to work on autonomous vehicle technology</b> and you\'re true to the name. This is an accelerated process with the company\'s getting just six months to achieve great things. So joining me now in the studio are representatives from two of the winning Cos John Proctor is CEO of communication services for Martello Technologies. Stephen Borsa is CEO for cyber security company Blue Ink Limited, and Leo Lacks is here, too. He\'s executive manager with the director division of El Spark. Nice to have you guys all in studio this afternoon. With only six months, you won\'t have much time to spare, so I appreciate the time you\'ve given us believe I want to start with you. Many of us still think of BlackBerry is the smart phone company that people, you know launched all that. But their research on autonomous vehicles has kind of taken over focus. What is the point of this partnership? So the key elements of the partnership is really a mechanism by which each of the groups are getting the benefit ofthe collaboration on a BlackBerry side. The Cue and Exide. They get access to innovation so fast moving ideas and companies that are going to putting together applications, they\'re going to be useful toe there and customer in some way. At the same time, the Little Cos the smaller companies who are joining the program are getting benefit from the platform that blackberry in Q Knicks have in a market. So your job was to locate suitable partners in this sphere that\'s got a rarefied the area of technology. What what were you looking for? What were the kind of criteria? So actually, in this particular case as a corporate accelerator, we worked with Q nicks to actually define the kind of companies that they were looking for in the early stage companies territory that they thought would be best fit, the areas that their customers would be looking at. So they were areas such as, of course, the autonomous vehicle area. Unix is also being used, and many of the utilities first generation networks as well as in a medical device area. So we put out our notices to say, anybody interested in building applications off those types that are built on this platform should come and see us. And they did. So you give me some sense How many people were knocking on your door when you put out the call? So that\'s a good questions. So we actually this was a fairly a fast paced programme. Over a two month period. We had about a hundred applicants out of which we selected, ten, who then presented their ideas, tow the BlackBerry and the Allspark team, and we selected out of those seven. Okay, so I want to bring in John and Stephen now on DH. I think what\'s needed at this point in a high tech conversation? Steven, Maybe in a simple way, you can tell me what it is your company can add to this to this team. Absolutely. Esso Blue Ink is a a cyber security company, digital identity company that uses your smartphone as a token to log you into everything. So a lot of people talk about password free Loggins. How do you do that? Wait. Do that with your smartphone, Basically type in a random identify WR that points to your phone. Your phone goes, Bing says. Approve logging into a website and we log you in. Simple as that, and we\'ve just completed a proof of concept with the Ontario government to allow you to carry your driver\'s license, your health card, all of your IEDs on your phone and stuff in your wallet and use that ID to log into government websites or personal websites that you want to look into. And our next step in the identity everywhere is allow you to open your front door securely with the same identity and, in the case of this BlackBerry project, allow you to open a car door with your digital identity and allowed to be used for car sharing. So simply put, your phone will be your digital identity everywhere. I just five minutes before this interview, I went across the street to try to buy a coffee with no cash in my wallet, and my phone wouldn\'t pay for the coffee. I put it down on the reader, and it is your system going to work better than my phone did happen. Omar. It\'ll definitely okay. It\'ll death. Good cause we got locked out of your car because your phone goes dead. Something could be a problem. You can still use her key. OK, that\'s well, that\'s charge your phone. Okay, That\'s true, John. Same question free. What do you hope to bring to this incubator? This project, if you\'re so, what Martello does is make networks perform better. So when you got real time services like video conferencing, voice over I p any real time services, very sensitive networks. We just make that work across the Internet. What we\'re doing here is actually fairly complicated. Imagine this vehicle. You know, Autonomous vehicle driving along is gonna have multiple connections to Bell to Rogers to tell us we want to make sure that we\'ve got the best connectivity for that network. It always stays up on. We\'re privatizing traffic, you know? Think about the autonomous vehicle. You know, if there\'s nobody driving, people are gonna be watching videos, playing games in the back, doing whatever. Well, what\'s the most important traffic coming out of the car? His security is making sure that vehicle is talking to the smart city. Is talking to the road is talking to other vehicles and not to the Netflix, sir. I\'m not a Netflix server, so exactly. So we want to prioritise that to make sure that that always stays connected for the safety and security individuals inside the car. I don\'t suppose you\'re going to give away your white papers on this, but what\'s in it in a simple term? What\'s what\'s the challenge of that? How do you make a certain data packet? I guess prioritized over the other junk. The challenges really doing this speed, right? If I\'m sitting in a building like this to sitting here, it can work out here\'s all the the the cell phone towers around me. I can connect to them. Great. But when you\'ve never been on via rail, gonna Montreal, Toronto, your call drops because phones are designed to constantly battle over to sell to. You can\'t afford that in an autonomous vehicle. We want to make sure that never happens, and you always stay connected. I\'ll ask both Stephen and John. How old is your company? Were described to startups. But how recent is this beginning? So we\'re a sort of nine year overnight success. But again, sort of, You know, we went public this year, so I was kind of our sort of big pieces here. We wanted a few tech companies here in town to go public, so we\'re not, as a start up should be were still fairly small under a hundred people. But again, it\'s also part of going through the the process of BlackBerry. We\'ve been identified. BlackBerries with Q and ex is something they need. And that was part of the process for us is to actually rather than build it and hope black, relax it were working with the black Rick. You\'re next team directly developed something they\'ve already identified to develop something that actually fits very well into the program. Steven, how old is your company? So I incorporated the company back in two thousand ten and Maura\'s RND consultancy. I got tired of working for other people here that people tell me what to do. However, my past has always been product development and doing new things. So I got itchy feet a couple years in and started building products as well as doing the RND side. I had the opportunity to add a CTO to my company. Larry Hammond, who had worked with on a couple of different start ups over the years back in the nineties and the two thousands, and he joined me in twenty fifteen, and we re focused on digital identity space, which was actually what we\'ve done in our past to companies and really, the phone as a password manager and phone is an authenticator to everything. What does on opportunity like this to work with BlackBerry and Ellis Park? What does it represent for your company? But I gather notice doesn\'t go up in Kannada saying, Hey, whatever technology working on we wanted because working in the special project that everyone\'s eyes are on, I gather it\'s a rare opportunity. What is it? What does it mean for your company? For us, that blue ink, it means our vision of doors to desktop security. So, as I said, being I\'ll open the front door on them being ableto log into a computer, we can achieve that with BlackBerry. You know, we looked at cars and said, Okay, how would you open occur while every car is different? But at the core of one hundred twenty million cars in the world is the BlackBerry Q and ex operating system So if we want to connect to the most cars from all different manufacturers, doing it through the queue and ex operating system is is the place for us to be toe Realize this vision and sixteen people in Ottawa, I can\'t address one hundred twenty million cars. But going through the Cuban ex operating system allows us to get global coverage that we could never achieve with a similar are kind of a access of scale for your company, too. Is that what you\'d say about what it represents for you? Yes. And on top of that, it also access to the Cuban ex engineers and senior executives themselves, because again, you want to run inside their environment. So you need their expertise to come back to you and give guidance and advice. So having that in a programmatic way, where we know we reach out, we know we\'ll get responses. And we can have this back when board\'s eyes absolutely key to success in this. As you said, fairly short six months project. You guys are all dressed like businessmen, and so I know you\'ll have the manners of businessmen, but I think it\'s fair that you\'re staking your put this on the radio? Yeah, that one\'s going on their best manners, but it\'s got to be said, This is a leap of faith, You guys. We\'re putting a considerable number of eggs in this basket, and nobody knows the honest whether BlackBerry Q. Nix is the solution to autonomous cars as well. Experience meant fifty. Why make this this deal with this company now? Well, for us, we see the obvious first step is car sharing. So millennials young people, they\'re not running out on my neck are sixteen. They\'re either going to be a member of a car share service or say you could lease a vehicle and put it into a car share fleet and let your car be used. Paid off by someone else. Let them. You\'re driving for free If you let your car be used six days a month when you\'re not using it all of a sudden you\'re you have a cool car and it cost you nothing. So that\'s the sharing economy. Airbnb for cars is really our vision. And what about you? Why take this scandal with Kunitz? How do you mean? You\'re going to say something polite as I\'ve already said because you were going to Jack and I can tell, but how do you know this is the right way? Well, again, it\'s your We\'re focused on autonomous vehicles, but Q and exes in other things as well. It\'s the Internet of things. So is that broader market as well? So muchas we\'re interested in the vehicles. If you could do this in a vehicle, you can do this in a train. You can do this in the aeroplane on, Then you\'re extending this into that smart city environment. So really it\'s, you know, Q. Necks. You know, they\'re focuses much. Is its autonomous vehicles here in Kannada. They\'re in many other spaces as well, so it\'s been able to step into that area as well. And when you make a deal with the else bark and the BlackBerry people, does it mean once thie incubated period is over, you\'re free to continue doing RD with other companies. Or how does that relationship work? After the sunset of the Thie incubator? I think the key really is someone had gone through the summer into the business terms. Right? Let\'s get this up and running. Then let\'s say Yes, it\'s working as it\'s not working and then start looking the business piece so much as you said, we\'ve got to get the technology to work. We\'ve also have the business piece that works as well to make sure that, you know, provide value to both sides. Leo, I wonder what you see is happening after six months of one. If you learned anything, this art, I think that these guys tell you what you wanted to hear or like What? This? Well, so there are a couple of things that really key to our environment here. One is all of the existing companies right now in the world. The major platform companies are no longer doing everything themselves. They all collaborate with others to ensure that they get the best of breed mechanism to do. There are difficult, so they need in intermediaries. That happened to that house. Park is one of those things. What we\'re getting out of this is building an ecosystem right here in Canada. Que nix is one of the shining lights in Canada, and we believe that by allowing our innovation groups connecting to the rest of the organizations and getting capabilities and clinics to grow them bigger were not only helping Q. Nixon the companies, but our entire ecosystem. It\'s fascinating. And I got to confess. It\'s rare that we get a chance to talk to the guys who were coming from cannot and working those big beige building. So fascinating you guys should come visit us more often. Were were you not aware, Jack? And Okay, I\'ve never wearing a jacket again. Wei are Bronson and Gladstone\'s. Sorry, we\'re not in the west and you\'re way Prefer where we can get his restaurants on foot. Nice to meet you all. Thanks a lot for coming in this afternoon. Thank you. Pleasure. Thank you. Thanks for listening to the all in a day podcast. More stories from the show are available on our website cbc dot slash, all in a day. For more CBC podcasts, go to cbc dot see a slash podcasts.</string>

    <string name="podcast_3_claire">This is a CBC podcast. Hi, I\'m Jamie. Puts on For the last decade, I\'ve been a newspaper reporter, and lately I\'m just finding it hard to keep up with the news. As of today, simple possession of marijuana is no longer illegal. It can be hard to make sense of things. Investigators spent nine hours in the consulate\'s appearance or murder. I want to change that. At least a little. I hope you\'ll join me for front burner at daily podcast from CBC News. Subscribe now wherever you get your podcasts. Hi there. I\'m Alan Neil, and welcome to the All in a day podcast where every weekday we try to pick one conversation from today\'s edition of all in a day. So here\'s today\'s now three promising tech companies from Ottawa got some great news Just ahead of the holidays. The Kanada based L Spark teamed up with BlackBerry Q. Nick\'s recently to create an accelerator program with seven spots up for grabs. They choose three local companies to work on autonomous vehicle technology and you\'re true to the name. This is an accelerated process with the company\'s getting just six months to achieve great things. So joining me now in the studio are representatives from two of the winning Cos John Proctor is CEO of communication services for Martello Technologies. Stephen Borsa is CEO for cyber security company Blue Ink Limited, and Leo Lacks is here, too. He\'s executive manager with the director division of El Spark. Nice to have you guys all in studio this afternoon. With only six months, you won\'t have much time to spare, so I appreciate the time you\'ve given us believe I want to start with you. Many of us still think of BlackBerry is the smart phone company that people, you know launched all that. But their research on autonomous vehicles has kind of taken over focus. What is the point of this partnership? So the key elements of the partnership is really a mechanism by which each of the groups are getting the benefit ofthe collaboration on a BlackBerry side. The Cue and Exide. They get access to innovation so fast moving ideas and companies that are going to putting together applications, they\'re going to be useful toe there and customer in some way. At the same time, the Little Cos the smaller companies who are joining the program are getting benefit from the platform that blackberry in Q Knicks have in a market. So your job was to locate suitable partners in this sphere that\'s got a rarefied the area of technology. What what were you looking for? What were the kind of criteria? So actually, in this particular case as a corporate accelerator, we worked with Q nicks to actually define the kind of companies that they were looking for in the early stage companies territory that they thought would be best fit, the areas that their customers would be looking at. So they were areas such as, of course, the autonomous vehicle area. Unix is also being used, and many of the utilities first generation networks as well as in a medical device area. So we put out our notices to say, anybody interested in building applications off those types that are built on this platform should come and see us. And they did. So you give me some sense How many people were knocking on your door when you put out the call? So that\'s a good questions. So we actually this was a fairly a fast paced programme. Over a two month period. We had about a hundred applicants out of which we selected, ten, who then presented their ideas, tow the BlackBerry and the Allspark team, and we selected out of those seven. Okay, so I want to bring in John and Stephen now on DH. I think what\'s needed at this point in a high tech conversation? Steven, Maybe in a simple way, you can tell me what it is your company can add to this to this team. Absolutely. Esso Blue Ink is a a cyber security company, digital identity company that uses your smartphone as a token to log you into everything. So a lot of people talk about password free Loggins. How do you do that? Wait. Do that with your smartphone, Basically type in a random identify WR that points to your phone. Your phone goes, Bing says. Approve logging into a website and we log you in. Simple as that, and we\'ve just completed a proof of concept with the Ontario government to allow you to carry your driver\'s license, your health card, all of your IEDs on your phone and stuff in your wallet and use that ID to log into government websites or personal websites that you want to look into. And our next step in the identity everywhere is allow you to open your front door securely with the same identity and, in the case of this BlackBerry project, allow you to open a car door with your digital identity and allowed to be used for car sharing. <b>So simply put, your phone will be your digital identity everywhere. I just five minutes before this interview, I went across the street to try to buy a coffee with no cash in my wallet, and my phone wouldn\'t pay for the coffee. I put it down on the reader, and it is your system going to work better than my phone did happen. Omar. It\'ll definitely okay. It\'ll death. Good cause we got locked out of your car because your phone goes dead. Something could be a problem.</b> You can still use her key. OK, that\'s well, that\'s charge your phone. Okay, That\'s true, John. Same question free. What do you hope to bring to this incubator? This project, if you\'re so, what Martello does is make networks perform better. So when you got real time services like video conferencing, voice over I p any real time services, very sensitive networks. We just make that work across the Internet. What we\'re doing here is actually fairly complicated. Imagine this vehicle. You know, Autonomous vehicle driving along is gonna have multiple connections to Bell to Rogers to tell us we want to make sure that we\'ve got the best connectivity for that network. It always stays up on. We\'re privatizing traffic, you know? Think about the autonomous vehicle. You know, if there\'s nobody driving, people are gonna be watching videos, playing games in the back, doing whatever. Well, what\'s the most important traffic coming out of the car? His security is making sure that vehicle is talking to the smart city. Is talking to the road is talking to other vehicles and not to the Netflix, sir. I\'m not a Netflix server, so exactly. So we want to prioritise that to make sure that that always stays connected for the safety and security individuals inside the car. I don\'t suppose you\'re going to give away your white papers on this, but what\'s in it in a simple term? What\'s what\'s the challenge of that? How do you make a certain data packet? I guess prioritized over the other junk. The challenges really doing this speed, right? If I\'m sitting in a building like this to sitting here, it can work out here\'s all the the the cell phone towers around me. I can connect to them. Great. But when you\'ve never been on via rail, gonna Montreal, Toronto, your call drops because phones are designed to constantly battle over to sell to. You can\'t afford that in an autonomous vehicle. We want to make sure that never happens, and you always stay connected. I\'ll ask both Stephen and John. How old is your company? Were described to startups. But how recent is this beginning? So we\'re a sort of nine year overnight success. But again, sort of, You know, we went public this year, so I was kind of our sort of big pieces here. We wanted a few tech companies here in town to go public, so we\'re not, as a start up should be were still fairly small under a hundred people. But again, it\'s also part of going through the the process of BlackBerry. We\'ve been identified. BlackBerries with Q and ex is something they need. And that was part of the process for us is to actually rather than build it and hope black, relax it were working with the black Rick. You\'re next team directly developed something they\'ve already identified to develop something that actually fits very well into the program. Steven, how old is your company? So I incorporated the company back in two thousand ten and Maura\'s RND consultancy. I got tired of working for other people here that people tell me what to do. However, my past has always been product development and doing new things. So I got itchy feet a couple years in and started building products as well as doing the RND side. I had the opportunity to add a CTO to my company. Larry Hammond, who had worked with on a couple of different start ups over the years back in the nineties and the two thousands, and he joined me in twenty fifteen, and we re focused on digital identity space, which was actually what we\'ve done in our past to companies and really, the phone as a password manager and phone is an authenticator to everything. What does on opportunity like this to work with BlackBerry and Ellis Park? What does it represent for your company? But I gather notice doesn\'t go up in Kannada saying, Hey, whatever technology working on we wanted because working in the special project that everyone\'s eyes are on, I gather it\'s a rare opportunity. What is it? What does it mean for your company? For us, that blue ink, it means our vision of doors to desktop security. So, as I said, being I\'ll open the front door on them being ableto log into a computer, we can achieve that with BlackBerry. You know, we looked at cars and said, Okay, how would you open occur while every car is different? But at the core of one hundred twenty million cars in the world is the BlackBerry Q and ex operating system So if we want to connect to the most cars from all different manufacturers, doing it through the queue and ex operating system is is the place for us to be toe Realize this vision and sixteen people in Ottawa, I can\'t address one hundred twenty million cars. But going through the Cuban ex operating system allows us to get global coverage that we could never achieve with a similar are kind of a access of scale for your company, too. Is that what you\'d say about what it represents for you? Yes. And on top of that, it also access to the Cuban ex engineers and senior executives themselves, because again, you want to run inside their environment. So you need their expertise to come back to you and give guidance and advice. So having that in a programmatic way, where we know we reach out, we know we\'ll get responses. And we can have this back when board\'s eyes absolutely key to success in this. As you said, fairly short six months project. You guys are all dressed like businessmen, and so I know you\'ll have the manners of businessmen, but I think it\'s fair that you\'re staking your put this on the radio? Yeah, that one\'s going on their best manners, but it\'s got to be said, This is a leap of faith, You guys. We\'re putting a considerable number of eggs in this basket, and nobody knows the honest whether BlackBerry Q. Nix is the solution to autonomous cars as well. Experience meant fifty. Why make this this deal with this company now? Well, for us, we see the obvious first step is car sharing. So millennials young people, they\'re not running out on my neck are sixteen. They\'re either going to be a member of a car share service or say you could lease a vehicle and put it into a car share fleet and let your car be used. Paid off by someone else. Let them. You\'re driving for free If you let your car be used six days a month when you\'re not using it all of a sudden you\'re you have a cool car and it cost you nothing. So that\'s the sharing economy. Airbnb for cars is really our vision. And what about you? Why take this scandal with Kunitz? How do you mean? You\'re going to say something polite as I\'ve already said because you were going to Jack and I can tell, but how do you know this is the right way? Well, again, it\'s your We\'re focused on autonomous vehicles, but Q and exes in other things as well. It\'s the Internet of things. So is that broader market as well? So muchas we\'re interested in the vehicles. If you could do this in a vehicle, you can do this in a train. You can do this in the aeroplane on, Then you\'re extending this into that smart city environment. So really it\'s, you know, Q. Necks. You know, they\'re focuses much. Is its autonomous vehicles here in Kannada. They\'re in many other spaces as well, so it\'s been able to step into that area as well. And when you make a deal with the else bark and the BlackBerry people, does it mean once thie incubated period is over, you\'re free to continue doing RD with other companies. Or how does that relationship work? After the sunset of the Thie incubator? I think the key really is someone had gone through the summer into the business terms. Right? Let\'s get this up and running. Then let\'s say Yes, it\'s working as it\'s not working and then start looking the business piece so much as you said, we\'ve got to get the technology to work. We\'ve also have the business piece that works as well to make sure that, you know, provide value to both sides. Leo, I wonder what you see is happening after six months of one. If you learned anything, this art, I think that these guys tell you what you wanted to hear or like What? This? Well, so there are a couple of things that really key to our environment here. One is all of the existing companies right now in the world. The major platform companies are no longer doing everything themselves. They all collaborate with others to ensure that they get the best of breed mechanism to do. There are difficult, so they need in intermediaries. That happened to that house. Park is one of those things. What we\'re getting out of this is building an ecosystem right here in Canada. Que nix is one of the shining lights in Canada, and we believe that by allowing our innovation groups connecting to the rest of the organizations and getting capabilities and clinics to grow them bigger were not only helping Q. Nixon the companies, but our entire ecosystem. It\'s fascinating. And I got to confess. It\'s rare that we get a chance to talk to the guys who were coming from cannot and working those big beige building. So fascinating you guys should come visit us more often. Were were you not aware, Jack? And Okay, I\'ve never wearing a jacket again. Wei are Bronson and Gladstone\'s. Sorry, we\'re not in the west and you\'re way Prefer where we can get his restaurants on foot. Nice to meet you all. Thanks a lot for coming in this afternoon. Thank you. Pleasure. Thank you. Thanks for listening to the all in a day podcast. More stories from the show are available on our website cbc dot slash, all in a day. For more CBC podcasts, go to cbc dot see a slash podcasts.</string>


</resources>
